LIAUREN PERMATA SARI

liaurenpermata22@gmail.com +62823 2566 8322

linkedin.com/in/liauren-permata-sari | github.com/liaurenpermata

A person who is **very passionate** about technology and **never stops learning** about software development. Have spent two years improving skills in **Website Development** with proven experience in several projects. Able to work in a team and have experience to lead, enhance, and develop tech organizations. Currently, looking for a **Frontend Engineer Intern** opportunity.

EDUCATION

BINA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY

(September 2020 – Present)

Bachelor, Computer Science, GPA 3.70

Relevant Coursework: Algorithm and Programming, Program Design Method, Data Structure, Human and Computer Interaction, Database System, Artificial Intelligence, Computer Networks, Algorithm Design and Analysis, Software Engineering, Mobile Community Solution, Embedded System, Object Oriented Programming, Calculus

PROJECT EXPERIENCES

Lili Sistech - Website App (2022)

- A web app platform for people to share and ask questions implemented **REST API** with **JSON data**.
- Role as Frontend Developer. Tech stacks: React.js, Bootstrap, CSS.

Repo: https://github.com/liaurenpermata/lili-sistech-app

Anime App - Website App (2022)

- An app list for the most popular anime in the world using **API fetch** data and **routing navigation**.
- Role as Frontend Developer. Tech stacks: React.js and CSS

Repo: https://github.com/liaurenpermata/AnimeReactApp

InSOrma - Mobile App (2022)

- A furniture shop mobile application built with other 2 members.
- Role as a mobile developer that has successfully developed recyclerview list API, maps googleAPI, and Sms service.
 Tech stacks: Java.

Repo: https://github.com/liaurenpermata/InSOrma

Quori - Website App (2020)

- A web app blog platform to post and answer that successfully built a backend database and RESTFUL API.
- Role as Fullstack Developer. Tech stacks: Laravel, Bootstrap, SQL.

Repo: https://github.com/liaurenpermata/FinalProject-BNCCFullstack2020

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCES

Bina Nusantara Computer Club (BNCC)

(January 2022 - Present)

Chief Financial Officer Bandung

- Negotiated event agreements with 5+ startups and other partners.
- Chaired the first corporate social responsibility "Data Science" event in BNCC and reached more than 200% participants target.

HIMTI Binus Bandung

(September 2020 - July 2021)

Tutor Teacher

- Teach fellow students to increase their score every review session before mid and final exam.
- Course: Linear Algebra, Discrete Mathematics, Calculus.

SKILLS

Programming Languages : C/C++, Javascript, Java, Python, PHP, SQL, NoSQL

Frameworks: React.js, Redux, Next.js, Vue.js, Laravel, Bootstrap

Skills: Data Structure & Algorithm, Software Architectures, Competitive Programming, OOP, Product Management, Scrum, Communication, Analytical Skill, Problem Solving

Tools: Git, MySQL, Android Studio, Figma, Visual Studio Code, Eclipse